<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">YGO Database</string>
    <string name="adUnitId">ca-app-pub-8564595162671342/8183570114</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Drawer open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Drawer close</string>
    
    <string name="help_text">
<![CDATA[
        <h1> General </h1>
        <b>Q: How often is this app\'s data updated?</b> <br/>
        A: If you are connected to the internet, this app pulls all data from the Yugioh Wikia in real time, so the data is always up-to-date. <br/><br/>
        If you are offline, this app uses an offline database, which is updated about once a month. <br/><br/>
        
        <b>Q: If the app\'s information is always up-to-date, why don\'t the latest changes in the Wikia show up in the app?</b> <br/>
        A: This app does some caching for performance reason, so you can force close and restart it to force it to load the latest data. <br/><br/>
        
        <b>Q: I like this app!</b> <br/>
        A: I\'m glad to hear it. Please rate it on the Play Store :) <br/><br/>
        Also if you don\'t like the ads, you may consider getting the ads-free version on the Play store (its name is \"YGO Database Pro\").<br/><br/>
        
        <b>Q: This app sucks!/I found a bug/This is not useful/I have a suggestion...</b> <br/>
        A: Please drop me a line at chinho.dev@gmail.com and let me know how I can improve it. Thank you :)<br/><br/>
      ]]>
    </string>
    
    <string name="about_text">
        YGO Database
        \nCopyright Chin 2014
    </string>
    
    <string name="about_text_pro">
        YGO Database Pro
        \nCopyright Chin 2014
    </string>
    
    <string name="about_text_part2">
        This app is not authorized or created by the authors or legal representatives of "Yu-Gi-Oh!". 
        This application complies with US Copyright law guidelines of "fair use". If you feel there is a direct copyright 
        or trademark violation that doesn\'t follow within the "fair use" guidelines please contact us to discuss. 
        All characters and their names, places, events and all other aspects concerning the "Yu-Gi-Oh!" are the 
        property of their respective owners. All trademark and copyright concerning the "Yu-Gi-Oh!" series are the  
        property of their respective owners. We make no claim to and do not have any rights to any of the foregoing. Image  
        in this application icon is used only to convey what the application is about. \n\n

        Information used by this app is taken from the Yu-Gi-Oh! Wikia. This information is freely available under the terms of the Creative Commons CC-BY-SA 3.0 License. \n\n

        This app is not affiliated with the Yu-Gi-Oh! Wikia. \n\n
        
        This app uses the jsoup and Universal Image Loader open source libraries.
    </string>
</resources>
